ANA LUNA

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



(619)301-0973



luna.ana92@gmail.com



San Diego, CA



linkedin.com/in/analuna01

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Full Stack Developer student at UCSD-Extension based in San Diego, CA. With a background in Psychology and experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and JQuery I have acquire the skills necessary to build professional, interactive and user-friendly applications.

EDUCATION

CERTIFICATE IN PROCESS // FULL STACK DEVELOPER

UCSD-EXTENSION, San Diego, CA 2020-Present

DEGREE IN PRCOCESS // PSYCHOLOGY

CAL STATE SAN MARCOS, San Marcos, CA 2018

Associates Degrees //
Psychology & Liberal Arts
MiraCosta College, Oceanside,
CA
2012-2017

EXPERTISE

- HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY
- MYSQL
- Project Development
- APIs
- New Business Development
- Account Management
- Client Needs Assessment
- Social Media Management

WORK EXPERIENCE

Business Manager

Êvolv Hair Parlor | San Diego, CA | 2016 - Present

- Established this business with my husband and as the business manager I am responsible of making sure every guideline is met.
- Manage business social media and marketing.
- Develop new ideas for future business growth.
- Manage business accounts and other financial aspects.
- Problem solver abilities.
- Attention to detail in every aspect of the business.
- Strong mathematical and critical thinking skills.

RELATIONSHIP BANKER

Bank of America | Escondido, CA | 2011 – 2017

- Assessed clients' financial needs and provided a solution.
- Responsible of opening and closing duties.
- Established strong banking relationships with clients and businesses.
- Constant communication with other bankers, investing and mortgage consultants.
- Personal computer and data entry experience.
- Knowledge in banking software and terminology.
- Strong mathematical and critical thinking skills.
- Ability to work both independently and as part of a team.

UCSD-Extention

Bootcamp Projects:

Web Development

PROFESSIONAL PORTFOLIO

As part of our career growth in web development, it is important that we create a professional website that describes who we are and what we can do.

Github URL: https://github.com/analuna01/

ProfessionalPortfolio-hw7

Deployed URL: https://analuna01.github.io/

ProfessionalPortfolio-hw7/

OUTDOOR ITINERARY

This was a group project in which we created an application that would allow the user to plan an outdoor adventure by saving their activities in an agenda while having access to a search engine that would allow them to search for a restaurant or recreation in a given city.

Github URL: https://github.com/christ-ine/outdoor-itinerary/
Deployed URL: https://christ-ine.github.io/outdoor-itinerary/

WEATHER DASHBOARD

The goal for this project was to create a weather dashboard that included a search section where the user can look for a city and the current weather conditions would display along with a five day forecast.

Github URL: https://github.com/analuna01/WeatherDashboard-

hw6.git

Deployed URL: https://analuna01.github.io/WeatherDashboard-

<u>hw6/</u>